(Sheldon:)about what happened
earlier between us.
(Sheldon:)Also, I had one heck of a bus nap.
(Sheldon:)Speaking of which, do you want
some mutton in coconut milk?
(Penny:)-No.
-I cannot give this stuff away.
(Amy:)What do you want?
(Sheldon:)Amy, this isn't easy to say.
(Sheldon:)All relationships are difficult,
(Sheldon:)but even more so
when you're in one
(Sheldon:)with a person who struggles
with everyday social interactions
(Sheldon:)and, frankly, who can strike some
people as being kind of a weirdo.
(Penny:)Sheldon...
you're not a weirdo.
(Sheldon:)I wasn't speaking about me.
(Sheldon:)I mean, honestly, there's no telling
what will set you off.
(Sheldon:)You know, introducing myself
as your boyfriend.
(Sheldon:)Giving you the opportunity
to drive me home.
(Sheldon:)Breaking the ice with your colleagues
using ethnic humor,
the funniest kind of humor.
(Amy:)-What's your point?
-My point is, we're a couple.
(Penny:)And...
I like you for who you are.
(Sheldon:)Quirks and all.
(Amy:)-I like you, too.
-Well, I should hope so.
(Sheldon:)I don't see anyone else
banging on this door
(Sheldon:)to put up with your nonsense.
(Sheldon:)Not even a good-bye?
(Sheldon:)You see, that's the kind of thing
that makes people think you're weird.
Go away.
(Sheldon:)Poor kid.
(Sheldon:)She just doesn't see it.
(Bernadette:)I'm not apologizing to Howard.
(Bernadette:)He can come beg me on his knees.
(Amy:)Sheldon, too. If I see him at work,
I'm just going to ignore him.
(Penny:)All right, don't worry.
I talked to Leonard.
(Penny:)He is gonna sit the guys down
and set them straight.
(Leonard:)Laser's warmed up.
Pull!